There are also two areas here
Where Palestinians have more or less influence and rule.
I'm not going to go into it in detail - it's sensitive.
Thanks, Anders Kraft.
- There wasn't much power in that, just Anders.
I'm not going to review journalists.
Going into detail is sensitive.
But I understand you, Anders.
Treads wrong on this question
is it easy to be accused of being Islamophobic or anti -Semit
Or if you are really customer: both.
It is very sensitive
And that's why we look at how this terror has been condemned in Sweden.
We start at the far right.
The civilized world stands behind Israel's right to defend itself.
We must be crystal clear that we are behind Israel at this moment.
We should freeze aid to Palestine immediately.
The Swedish right has longer had a pro-Israeli attitude.
SD has wanted a little back and forth in the Jewish issue.
But the Sosses have been more pro-Palestine since Palme
But now it has sounded like this:
It is important that the world speaks with a voice
both in condemning Hamas attack
And be clear that Israel has a legal right to defend itself.
When such a terrible thing happens
The Sosses must temporarily put away the Palestinian shawl.
Or shawl ... it's probably more a kind of scarf.
No scarf anyway.
The sisters in all glory - those who have really made it their thing
We find to support Palestine at the far left.
What did Nooshi Dadgostar say about this terrorist act?
We see an escalation.
In order not to be a carnage, a ceasefire is required.
Now the violence and attacks must cease.
Of course, this also applies to Israel.
Look there, it was well pragmatic.
Departure seems to be, but not for that Björn had intended.
In the afternoon the message came that the Left Party's party board
started an exclusion process against Björn Alling.
Sad for Björn, but he has great support within the party.
It has been started a name gathering against his exclusion
which over a hundred party mates have written on.
Remember that these are people who had been standing in Manhattan 9/11
Seen the plan hit the towers and demanded that Nooshi resign.
Not from the mediocre Arab pilots, but the US war crime.
We try something stronger.
I find some evil Hamas can do.
We feed in: "Hamas carries out the Holocaust 2.0."
And then I press the "Nooshi condemns" button.
There was criticism again.
Unbelievable.
It must be even more serious.
Now we release all the barriers.
I have to come up with something really damn sick that Hamas can do.
Oh, fuck.
"Hamas for free rental in new production."
And then we press the button.
No criticism!
The whole party supports it!